{
    "id": "83ae83c791e849deaacc3573e38832f5",
    "title": "Synonyms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The committee was not 'disposed' to hold another meeting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "inclined",
                "disorganized",
                "annoyed",
                "excited"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2fc29d973d4d494290265cbe6f93affa"
        },
        {
            "question": "The special TV report 'disrupted' regular programming.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "satisfied",
                "complemented",
                "interrupted",
                "continued"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2795bb2041da4b4786fe8f8a80882ee7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He 'dissipated' his inheritance in less than six months.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "accumulated",
                "wasted",
                "saved",
                "hoarded"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "157db39abf854339b54293fcfa69cc3e"
        },
        {
            "question": "If enough members 'dissent', the new bill won’t be approved.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "agree",
                "disagree",
                "support",
                "question"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7d85a81840884913af58a39b096d1aba"
        },
        {
            "question": "A thunderstorm came up and 'dispersed' the picnickers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gathered",
                "scattered",
                "summoned",
                "organized"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "72dba728b7954d79b541a9e45391c722"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy’s recklessness 'dismayed' his mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "impressed",
                "distressed",
                "pleased",
                "annoyed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "84978357d7f34077a978d1cc15e3dd5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The 'disguised' commandos slipped through the enemy’s defense.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "camouflaged",
                "skilled",
                "trained",
                "experienced"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cc8435ff26014854bef787f2362983e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Laws have been passed against religious 'discrimination'.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tolerance",
                "intolerance",
                "bias",
                "fanaticism"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a6cc239d6d134498a58f75a24bc76c59"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog luckily 'disgorged' the bone from his throat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expelled",
                "swallowed",
                "choked",
                "gulped"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cb24cc5239c845848980d54cd90326f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The plane would probably 'disintegrate' at that high speed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fuse",
                "crumble",
                "merge",
                "stop"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0d4c4d71efab4eceb850fb454cfefc17"
        }
    ]
}